<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PaySuper Documentation on PaySuper docs</title>
    <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in PaySuper Documentation on PaySuper docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Example markdown</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/markdown/</guid>
      <description>Title with a line Lorem markdownum pavent auras, surgit nunc cingentibus libet Laomedonque que est. Pastor An arbor filia foedat, ne fugit aliter, per. Helicona illas et callida neptem est Oresitrophos caput, dentibus est venit. Tenet reddite famuli praesentem fortibus, quaeque vis foret si frondes gelidos gravidae circumtulit inpulit armenta nativum.
Headings h1 Heading h2 Heading h3 Heading h4 Heading h5 Heading h6 Heading Notes  The note with padding example.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>After the payment</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/fulfillment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/fulfillment/</guid>
      <description>Your customer gets an email with the receipt and an extra email with the purchased Product or Products as soon as the transaction is complete. If your customer has purchased several game-keys for different DRM platforms, they get an email per DRM platform with a game key and instructions on how to activate the key on the target DRM store. At the same time you see that transaction on the Dashboard in PaySuper Admin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Client-side payment initialization</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/sdk-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/sdk-integration/</guid>
      <description>Payment initialization on the client-side The client-side payment initialization makes it possible to integrate a Checkout Form into your website using only frontend code.
It’s easy to embed PaySuper JS SDK with just a few lines of code to start a payment process and display a purchase status finally whithout any server-side code.
If your sales use cases are not filled, use the server-side payment initialization with PaySuper API instead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customizing Checkout</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/customization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/customization/</guid>
      <description>Customizing Checkout Learn about the different ways you can customize your Checkout.
Localization The Checkout Form is localized to 2 languages with 10 more translations coming soon.
You can choose the complete set of supported languages for the project and products descriptions on the Project Settings page in your PaySuper Dashboard.
Prefilling customer data Boost your payment conversion rate with a payment form pre-filled with your customer&amp;rsquo;s name and email.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going Live</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/live/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/live/</guid>
      <description>Below is a holistic view of the process from the very start to going live:  Complete the onboarding and fill in the info about your Projects and Products Implement PaySuper Checkout on your website Setup the webhooks on your backend Test that everything works fine in our sandbox We verify that you&amp;rsquo;re good to go live and flip the switch You can stop reading this text, instead do navigate to the Dashboard to see the first sales =)  Now let&amp;rsquo;s double check all the important details that you may have missed When you’re done with PaySuper Checkout integration and are thinking about going live, we suggest you refer to the points below to make sure you haven&amp;rsquo;t missed an important detail or two.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Payment initialization with token</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/token/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/token/</guid>
      <description>Payment initialization with token A token is an encrypted string that represents certain details of your customer, such as the user id, game and purchase parameters.
You can create a token before your customer intents to pay and use it in the future payments. For instance, you can create the token after a user has signed up or has logged in to your website or a game client. When your customer wants to pay for something you redirect them to the PaySuper-hosted Checkout Form to instantly complete a purchase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick start</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/quick-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/quick-start/</guid>
      <description>Payments Flow User Flow   Integration Flow   Quick start Step 1. Register a PaySuper Company account  Registration and onboarding     Sign up. Verify your email address with the delivered confirmation email. Follow the steps of a brief Welcome Onboarding. You are required to fill in the Banking info in Company Onboarding to be able create a project.  When you are ready to start selling you will need to fill in all your company details in Company Onboarding and the sign the documents in the License Agreement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Server-side payment initialization</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/integration/</guid>
      <description>Payment initialization on the server-side НАПИСАТЬ ОПИСАНИЕ ЭТОГО ПОДХОДА
If your sales use cases are not filled, use the client-side payment initialization with PaySuper JS SDK instead.
Step 1. Create a Checkout Order ID on your server Send the POST /api/v1/order to receive an Order ID. Learn more about the full list of parameters that can be used for instance the redirect URLs for successful and failed payments.
Simple Checkout To collect one-time payments it&amp;rsquo;s enough to have a Project ID and an acceptable amount with currency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testing Checkout</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/testing/</guid>
      <description>Testing the Payment Process The Payment Form integration should be tested in the Sandbox before going live.
The Sandbox provides full functionality but it only emulates processing, no actual bank transactions are made.
When using PaySuper JS SDK ensure that:
 Handlers for the events are displayed properly. The PaySuper object created with all required parameters or your token contains all desired parameters.  Incase of using the PaySuper API in your server-side code ensure that:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>