<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PaySuper Documentation</title>
    <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on PaySuper Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Example markdown</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/markdown/</guid>
      <description>Title with a line Lorem markdownum pavent auras, surgit nunc cingentibus libet Laomedonque que est. Pastor An arbor filia foedat, ne fugit aliter, per. Helicona illas et callida neptem est Oresitrophos caput, dentibus est venit. Tenet reddite famuli praesentem fortibus, quaeque vis foret si frondes gelidos gravidae circumtulit inpulit armenta nativum.
Headings h1 Heading h2 Heading h3 Heading h4 Heading h5 Heading h6 Heading Notes  The note with padding example.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/glossary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/glossary/</guid>
      <description> Terms:  PaySuper Checkout PaySuper JS SDK PaySuper API PaySuper PaySuper Dashboard  Payment form:  a Checkout Form a payment an order a token  PaySuper Dashboard Product and Projects:  a Project a Product a Project&amp;rsquo;s Secret key a Virtual currency an in-game currency a Game key a key-activated product a Virtual item a transaction  PaySuper Dashboard pages:  the Projects list page the Project settings page the Project webhooks page the Transactions page the Company Onboarding page the Banking info section  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>After the payment</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/fulfillment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/fulfillment/</guid>
      <description>After the payment When your customers successfully complete payments they are redirected to the success URL page that you passed in a request parameter. Typically, this is a page on your website that informs your customer that their payment was successful.
To fulfil the customer’s purchase you can make it in several ways:
Fulfilling purchases manually with the PaySuper Dashboard
Fulfilling purchases automatically with webhooks
Email receipts
Fulfilling purchases with the PaySuper Dashboard Every customers&amp;rsquo; payment is recorded as a new entry in the payments log shown on the Transactions page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analytics Integration</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/analytics-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/analytics-integration/</guid>
      <description>Analytics Integration It&amp;rsquo;s assumed that you have already integrated PaySuper Checkout via SDK and set up your Google Analytics account.
Integrate We&amp;rsquo;ve set up a Google Analytics data collection in a test mode inside PaySuper. After the Beta testing, we&amp;rsquo;ll release the analytics integration to use with a customer&amp;rsquo;s tracking ID.  Google Analytics You can track the following events:
   Category Action Description     userAction clickCloseCross Closing the form by click on the cross (for a modal window mode).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Client-side payment initialization</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/sdk-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/sdk-integration/</guid>
      <description>Payment initialization on the client-side The client-side payment initialization makes it possible to integrate a Checkout Form into your website using only frontend code.
It’s easy to embed PaySuper JS SDK with just a few lines of Javascript code to start a payment process and display a purchase status finally whithout any server-side code.
 HOW IT WORKS
Try out the payment sample or see the code on GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customizing Checkout</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/customization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/customization/</guid>
      <description>Customizing Checkout Learn about the different ways you can customize your Checkout.
Localization Dashboard
The Checkout Form is localized for 24 languages.
You can choose the complete set of supported languages for the project and products descriptions on the Project Settings page in your PaySuper Dashboard.
Prefilling customer data Token
Boost your payment conversion rate with a payment form pre-filled with your customer&amp;rsquo;s name and email. To have the payment form prefilled, you can generate a token to encrypt all required information about your customer&amp;rsquo;s intent to pay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going Live</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/live/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/live/</guid>
      <description>PaySuper Checkout integration checklist When you’re done with PaySuper Checkout integration and are thinking about going live, we suggest you refer to the points below to check that you&amp;rsquo;ve covered all the significant steps.
Complete the Company onboarding Dashboard
When you are ready to start selling you will need to fill in all your company details in Company Onboarding and sign the documents in the License Agreement.
 Before confirming your application we manually check each new account to ensure that our platform is attended only by companies who are related to the gaming industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Payment initialization with token</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/token/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/token/</guid>
      <description>Payment initialization with token A token is an encrypted string that represents certain details of your customer (such as the user ID, email and others), a game and purchase parameters.
You can create a token before your customer intents to pay and use it in the future payments. For instance, you can create the token after a user has signed up or has logged in to your website or a game client.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick start</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/quick-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/quick-start/</guid>
      <description>Payments Flow User Flow   Integration Flow   Quick start Step 1. Register a PaySuper Company account  Registration and onboarding     Sign up. Verify your email address with the delivered confirmation email. Follow the steps of a brief Welcome Onboarding. You are required to fill in the Banking info in the Company Onboarding to be able create a project. Note that the currency of the bank account must be the same as the Account Currency for payouts filled in the Banking info.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Receiving Payouts</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payouts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payouts/</guid>
      <description>Receiving Payouts Your customers&amp;rsquo; successful payments are stored on your PaySuper account balance and can be received to your bank account using Payouts.
Setting up your bank account to receive payouts When you are ready to start selling you will need to fill in all your company details in Company Onboarding.
Bank account details for payouts are required when filling in Company Onboarding.
Note that the currency of the bank account must be the same as the Account Currency for payouts filled in the Banking info.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Refunding payments</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/refunds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/refunds/</guid>
      <description>Refunding payments You can request to refund a charge in whole for a processed transaction. After requesting a refund it cannot be cancelled. PaySuper automatically sends email receipt to your customers whenever they have a refunded purchase.
The refund can be sent only to the same customer&amp;rsquo;s bank card was used in a payment. If the customer&amp;rsquo;s card is expired, the refund will be made to the reissued card.  The refund costs Notice that all refund fees are being paid by PaySuper, so they are free of charge for you, but the fees from the original charge are not returned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Server-side payment initialization</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/integration/</guid>
      <description>Payment initialization on the server-side The server-side payment initialization makes it possible to integrate a Checkout Form into your website or game client using PaySuper API. It’s easy to get a Checkout Form URL using an Order API request and render a payment form in a browser.
You can use PaySuper JS SDK for the client-side payment initialization to integrate a Checkout Form into your website only on the client-side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supported languages</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/localization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/localization/</guid>
      <description>Supported languages for PaySuper Checkout    Language ISO 639 Code     Arabic ar   Brazilian portuguese pt   Bulgarian bg   Chinese simplified zh   Chinese traditional zh   Czech cs   Danish da   English en   Finnish fi   French fr   German de   Greek el   Hebrew he   Italian it   Japanese ja   Korean ko   Polish pl   Portuguese pt   Russian ru   Spanish es   Swedish sv   Tai th   Turkish tr   Vietnamese vi    Questions?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testing Checkout</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/testing/</guid>
      <description>Testing the Payment Process The Payment Form integration should be tested in the Sandbox before going live.
The Sandbox provides full functionality but it only emulates processing, no actual bank transactions are made.
When using PaySuper JS SDK ensure that:
 Handlers for the events are displayed properly. The PaySuper object is created with all required parameters or a token.  If you&amp;rsquo;re using the PaySuper API in your server-side code then ensure that:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Declines and Failed Payments</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/declines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/declines/</guid>
      <description>Understanding Declines and Failed Payments During a payment process, a failure result can happen because of the typical reasons. For example, the customer may not have enough money on a bank card, or PaySuper Checkout may suspect a fraud attempt. If so, the payment status will be cancelled and a PaySuper Checkout notification event will contain an explanatory description.
But some reasons for the failed payments are unclear and uninformative.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>