<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PaySuper Documentation on PaySuper docs</title>
    <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in PaySuper Documentation on PaySuper docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Example markdown</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/markdown/</guid>
      <description>Title with a line Lorem markdownum pavent auras, surgit nunc cingentibus libet Laomedonque que est. Pastor An arbor filia foedat, ne fugit aliter, per. Helicona illas et callida neptem est Oresitrophos caput, dentibus est venit. Tenet reddite famuli praesentem fortibus, quaeque vis foret si frondes gelidos gravidae circumtulit inpulit armenta nativum.
Headings h1 Heading h2 Heading h3 Heading h4 Heading h5 Heading h6 Heading Notes  The note with padding example.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/glossary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/glossary/</guid>
      <description>Payment form: a Checkout Form
PaySuper Admin entities and properties: a Project
a Product
a Project Secret key
the Banking info
Virtual Currency
Game Keys
Virtual Items
a key-activated product
a virtual item
an in-game currency
PaySuper Admin pages: the Projects list page
the Project settings page
the Project Webhooks page
the Transactions page
Terms in lowercase: a payment
an order
a token
Terms in uppercase: PaySuper Checkout
Company Onboarding</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>After the payment</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/fulfillment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/fulfillment/</guid>
      <description>After the payment When your customers successfully complete payments they are redirected to the success URL page that you passed in a request parameter. Typically, this is a page on your website that informs your customer that their payment was successful.
At a later point, you may want to fulfill the customer’s purchase and deliver the goods or services they paid for. There are a few ways to do this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Client-side payment initialization</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/sdk-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/sdk-integration/</guid>
      <description>Payment initialization on the client-side The client-side payment initialization makes it possible to integrate a Checkout Form into your website using only frontend code.
It’s easy to embed PaySuper JS SDK with just a few lines of Javascript code to start a payment process and display a purchase status finally whithout any server-side code.
 HOW IT WORKS
Try out the payment sample or see the code on GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customizing Checkout</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/customization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/customization/</guid>
      <description>Customizing Checkout Learn about the different ways you can customize your Checkout.
Localization The Checkout Form is localized to 2 languages with 10 more translations coming soon.
You can choose the complete set of supported languages for the project and products descriptions on the Project Settings page in your PaySuper Dashboard.
Prefilling customer data Boost your payment conversion rate with a payment form pre-filled with your customer&amp;rsquo;s name and email.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going Live</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/live/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/live/</guid>
      <description>Below is a holistic view of the process from the very start to going live:  Complete the onboarding and fill in the info about your Projects and Products Implement PaySuper Checkout on your website Setup the webhooks on your backend Test that everything works fine in our sandbox We verify that you&amp;rsquo;re good to go live and flip the switch You can stop reading this text, instead do navigate to the Dashboard to see the first sales =)  Now let&amp;rsquo;s double check all the important details that you may have missed When you’re done with PaySuper Checkout integration and are thinking about going live, we suggest you refer to the points below to make sure you haven&amp;rsquo;t missed an important detail or two.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Payment initialization with token</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/token/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/token/</guid>
      <description>Payment initialization with token A token is an encrypted string that represents certain details of your customer (such as the user ID, email and others), a game and purchase parameters.
You can create a token before your customer intents to pay and use it in the future payments. For instance, you can create the token after a user has signed up or has logged in to your website or a game client.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick start</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/quick-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/quick-start/</guid>
      <description>Payments Flow User Flow   Integration Flow   Quick start Step 1. Register a PaySuper Company account  Registration and onboarding     Sign up. Verify your email address with the delivered confirmation email. Follow the steps of a brief Welcome Onboarding. You are required to fill in the Banking info in Company Onboarding to be able create a project.  When you are ready to start selling you will need to fill in all your company details in Company Onboarding and sign the documents in the License Agreement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Server-side payment initialization</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/integration/</guid>
      <description>Payment initialization on the server-side The server-side payment initialization makes it possible to integrate a Checkout Form into your website or game client using PaySuper API. It’s easy to get a Checkout Form URL using an Order API request and render a payment form in a browser.
You can use PaySuper JS SDK for the client-side payment initialization to integrate a Checkout Form into your website only on the client-side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testing Checkout</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/testing/</guid>
      <description>Testing the Payment Process The Payment Form integration should be tested in the Sandbox before going live.
The Sandbox provides full functionality but it only emulates processing, no actual bank transactions are made.
When using PaySuper JS SDK ensure that:
 Handlers for the events are displayed properly. The PaySuper object is created with all required parameters or token.  In case of using the PaySuper API in your server-side code ensure that:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testing currencies</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/currencies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/currencies/</guid>
      <description>Testing currencies    Currency Code Country and Currency     USD United States Dollar   EUR Euro Member Countries   GBP United Kingdom Pound   RUB Russia Ruble   BRL    JPY    IDR    MYR    PHP    SGD    THB    VND    KRW    TRY    MXN    CAD    AUD    NZD    NOK    PLN    CHF    CNY    INR    CLP    PEN    COP    ZAR    HKD    TWD    SAR    AED    ARS    ILS    KZT    QAR    CRC    HRK    CZK    RSD    RON    EGP    DKK    HUF    BHD    SEK     Questions?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Webhooks</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/about/webhooks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/about/webhooks/</guid>
      <description>Webhooks The PaySuper system can send you notifications for a set of events during the flow, such as creating new accounts or transaction flow, making payouts, and so on.
These notifications are sent as webhooks to the corresponding URLs configured on your Project settings page.
In most cases, webhooks are triggered by user actions on your website or back-end related events like refund a payment, notification about dispute and other.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>