<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Integration Overview on PaySuper</title>
    <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/getting-started/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Integration Overview on PaySuper</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Glossary</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/getting-started/glossary/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/getting-started/glossary/</guid>
      <description>PaySuper PaySuper is a payment service with a multifunctional toolkit that provides secure and immediate transactions online for games industry. Our mission is to maximize profits for developers, publishers, and platforms. We’re focused on keeping conversion rates high and costs low – including those related to integration and maintenance.
PaySuper JS SDK PaySuper’s JavaScript library is designed to integrate a PaySuper Payment Form on your website.
PaySuper API PaySuper public REST API server for a payment form and dashboards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manual Integration</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/getting-started/integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/getting-started/integration/</guid>
      <description>In the case of basic payment acceptance, the integration process takes just a few minutes.
Steps of the integration process:  To initiate a payment you can send a request with a secure string of an order parameters by POST /api/v1/tokens or key-value parameters about your Project and Products without a user information by POST /api/v1/order.
 After a customer initiates a payment retreive from a response a parameter payment_form_url - the payment form URL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Start</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/getting-started/quick-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/getting-started/quick-start/</guid>
      <description>Our mission is to maximize profits for developers, publishers, and platforms. We’re focused on keeping conversion rates high and costs low – including those related to integration and maintenance.
PaySuper was designed with developers in mind:
 The source code is available on the PaySuper GitHub, so you can follow the development process and see how everything actually works. PaySuper can be integrated into different platforms like a website, an online store or a game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testing</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/getting-started/testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/getting-started/testing/</guid>
      <description>Payment form integration should be tested in the PaySuper Sandbox before going live. PaySuper Sandbox provides full functionality but it only emulates processing, no actual bank transactions are made.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>External Reports</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/getting-started/external-reports/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/getting-started/external-reports/</guid>
      <description>When internal reports are not enough, you can connect an external analytics tool (for example, tableau or slemma) or your own data visualization tool.
You can access the data or, using the API, upload data to your storage. We adhere to the OLAP cube structure.
Dimensions:
 Project Product Geography Payment currency Payment method Payment date Return date User agent  Measures:
 The sum in payment currency The sum in payout currency Number of transactions  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Onboarding</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/getting-started/onboarding/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/getting-started/onboarding/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Account</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/getting-started/personal-account/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/getting-started/personal-account/</guid>
      <description> An account with PaySuper is the main point of interaction with PaySuper for all your employees.
The account contains tools for:  Account settings Project settings, including the launch of integration tests and product management Webhook configuration Transaction search, including full-text search for all attributes Returns management Dispute management Viewing reports and statistics Viewing and managing payouts Managing the rights of account users  The account supports:  Two-factor user authentication Real-time data updates Exporting all reports in CSV and XLSX formats  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project and Products</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/getting-started/project-products/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/getting-started/project-products/</guid>
      <description>The project-level management approach It allows you to independently configure PaySuper for use in various contexts:
 different games sites with different payment logic specialized solutions for a particular region or a specific cohort of users.  Any information about payments in this configuration can be reflected in the reports and analytics both cumulatively and separately.
Modes of operation in project Simple checkout In this mode, you transfer the payment sum for each specific transaction to PaySuper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reports Dashboard</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/getting-started/reports/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/getting-started/reports/</guid>
      <description>Examples of reports available on the dashboard and in the Reports section:
 Recent transactions. Revenue dynamics that can be broken down by project or product, with different levels of detail (day, week, month, year). Country statistics in the form of a table or heat map, where you can choose a period, projects and products. Returns report. Payouts report and a transactional report on a specific payout. Payment methods report, where you can choose a period, projects and products.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>