<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Checkout Overview on PaySuper Documentation</title>
    <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Checkout Overview on PaySuper Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>After the payment</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/fulfillment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/fulfillment/</guid>
      <description>After the payment When your customers successfully complete payments they are redirected to the success URL page that you passed in a request parameter. Typically, this is a page on your website that informs your customer that their payment was successful.
To fulfil the customer’s purchase you can make it in several ways:
Fulfilling purchases manually with the PaySuper Dashboard
Fulfilling purchases automatically with webhooks
Email receipts
Fulfilling purchases with the PaySuper Dashboard Every customers&amp;rsquo; payment is recorded as a new entry in the payments log shown on the Transactions page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Client-side payment initialization</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/sdk-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/sdk-integration/</guid>
      <description>Payment initialization on the client-side The client-side payment initialization makes it possible to integrate a Checkout Form into your website using only frontend code.
It’s easy to embed PaySuper JS SDK with just a few lines of Javascript code to start a payment process and display a purchase status finally without any server-side code.
 HOW IT WORKS
Try out the payment sample or see the code on GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customizing Checkout</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/customization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/customization/</guid>
      <description>Customizing Checkout Learn about the different ways you can customize your Checkout.
Localization Dashboard
The Checkout Form is localized for 24 languages.
You can choose the complete set of supported languages for the project and products descriptions on the Project Settings page in your PaySuper Dashboard.
Prefilling customer data Token
Boost your payment conversion rate with a payment form pre-filled with your customer&amp;rsquo;s name and email. To have the payment form prefilled, you can generate a token to encrypt all required information about your customer&amp;rsquo;s intent to pay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going Live</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/live/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/live/</guid>
      <description>PaySuper Checkout integration checklist When you’re done with PaySuper Checkout integration and are thinking about going live, we suggest you refer to the points below to check that you&amp;rsquo;ve covered all the significant steps.
Complete the Company onboarding Dashboard
When you are ready to start selling you will need to fill in all your company details in Company Onboarding and sign the documents in the License Agreement.
 Before confirming your application we manually check each new account to ensure that our platform is attended only by companies who are related to the gaming industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Payment initialization with token</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/token/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/token/</guid>
      <description>Payment initialization with token A token is an encrypted string that represents certain details of your customer (such as the user ID, email and others), a game and purchase parameters.
You can create a token before your customer intents to pay and use it in the future payments. For instance, you can create the token after a user has signed up or has logged in to your website or a game client.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick start</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/quick-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/quick-start/</guid>
      <description>Payments Flow User Flow   Integration Flow   Quick start Step 1. Register a PaySuper Company account  Registration and onboarding     Sign up. Verify your email address with the delivered confirmation email. Follow the steps of a brief Welcome Onboarding. You are required to fill in the Banking info in the Company Onboarding to be able create a project. Note that the currency of the bank account must be the same as the Account Currency for payouts filled in the Banking info.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Server-side payment initialization</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/integration/</guid>
      <description>Payment initialization on the server-side The server-side payment initialization makes it possible to integrate a Checkout Form into your website or game client using PaySuper API. It’s easy to get a Checkout Form URL using an Order API request and render a payment form in a browser.
You can use PaySuper JS SDK for the client-side payment initialization to integrate a Checkout Form into your website only on the client-side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supported languages</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/localization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/localization/</guid>
      <description>Supported languages for PaySuper Checkout    Language ISO 639 Code     Arabic ar   Brazilian portuguese pt   Bulgarian bg   Chinese simplified zh   Chinese traditional zh   Czech cs   Danish da   English en   Finnish fi   French fr   German de   Greek el   Hebrew he   Italian it   Japanese ja   Korean ko   Polish pl   Portuguese pt   Russian ru   Spanish es   Swedish sv   Tai th   Turkish tr   Vietnamese vi    Questions?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testing Checkout</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payments/testing/</guid>
      <description>Testing the Payment Process The Payment Form integration should be tested in the Sandbox before going live.
The Sandbox provides full functionality but it only emulates processing, no actual bank transactions are made.
When using PaySuper JS SDK ensure that:
 Handlers for the events are displayed properly. The PaySuper object is created with all required parameters or a token.  If you&amp;rsquo;re using the PaySuper API in your server-side code then ensure that:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>