<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Docs on PaySuper Documentation</title>
    <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docs on PaySuper Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Example markdown</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/markdown/</guid>
      <description>Title with a line Lorem markdownum pavent auras, surgit nunc cingentibus libet Laomedonque que est. Pastor An arbor filia foedat, ne fugit aliter, per. Helicona illas et callida neptem est Oresitrophos caput, dentibus est venit. Tenet reddite famuli praesentem fortibus, quaeque vis foret si frondes gelidos gravidae circumtulit inpulit armenta nativum.
Headings h1 Heading h2 Heading h3 Heading h4 Heading h5 Heading h6 Heading Notes  The note with padding example.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/glossary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/glossary/</guid>
      <description>Payment form: a Checkout Form
Terms in uppercase: PaySuper Checkout
PaySuper JS SDK
PaySuper API
PaySuper
PaySuper Dashboard
PaySuper Dashboard entities and properties: a Project
a Product
a Project&amp;rsquo;s Secret key
a Virtual currency
a Game key
a Virtual item
a key-activated product
a virtual item
an in-game currency
PaySuper Dashboard pages: the Projects list page
the Project settings page
the Project webhooks page
the Transactions page
the Company Onboarding page</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Webhooks</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/about/webhooks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/about/webhooks/</guid>
      <description>Webhooks The PaySuper system can send you notifications for a set of events during the flow, such as creating new accounts or transaction flow, making payouts, and so on.
These notifications are sent as webhooks to the corresponding URL configured on your Project Webhook page.
In most cases, webhooks are triggered by user actions on your website or back-end related events like a successful payment, refund payment and other.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>