<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Docs on PaySuper Documentation</title>
    <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docs on PaySuper Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Example markdown</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/markdown/</guid>
      <description>Title with a line Lorem markdownum pavent auras, surgit nunc cingentibus libet Laomedonque que est. Pastor An arbor filia foedat, ne fugit aliter, per. Helicona illas et callida neptem est Oresitrophos caput, dentibus est venit. Tenet reddite famuli praesentem fortibus, quaeque vis foret si frondes gelidos gravidae circumtulit inpulit armenta nativum.
Headings h1 Heading h2 Heading h3 Heading h4 Heading h5 Heading h6 Heading Notes  The note with padding example.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/glossary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/glossary/</guid>
      <description>Payment form: a Checkout Form
Terms in uppercase: PaySuper Checkout
PaySuper JS SDK
PaySuper API
PaySuper
PaySuper Dashboard
PaySuper Dashboard entities and properties: a Project
a Product
a Project&amp;rsquo;s Secret key
a Virtual currency
a Game key
a Virtual item
a key-activated product
a virtual item
an in-game currency
PaySuper Dashboard pages: the Projects list page
the Project settings page
the Project webhooks page
the Transactions page
the Company Onboarding page</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Receiving Payouts</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payouts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/payouts/</guid>
      <description>Receiving Payouts Your customers&amp;rsquo; successful payments are stored on your PaySuper account balance and can be received to your bank account using Payouts.
Setting up your bank account to receive payouts When you are ready to start selling you will need to fill in all your company details in Company Onboarding.
Bank account details for payouts are required when filling in Company Onboarding.
Note that the currency of the bank account must be the same as the Account Currency for payouts filled in the Banking info.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Refunding payments</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/refunds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/refunds/</guid>
      <description>Refunding payments You can request to refund a charge in whole for a processed transaction. After requesting a refund it cannot be cancelled. PaySuper automatically sends email receipt to your customers whenever they have a refunded purchase.
The refund can be sent only to the same customer&amp;rsquo;s bank card was used in a payment. If the customer&amp;rsquo;s card is expired, the refund will be made to the reissued card.  The refund costs Notice that all refund fees are being paid by PaySuper, so they are free of charge for you, but the fees from the original charge are not returned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Declines and Failed Payments</title>
      <link>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/declines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.stg.pay.super.com/docs/declines/</guid>
      <description>Understanding Declines and Failed Payments During a payment process, a failure result can happen because of the typical reasons. For example, the customer may not have enough money on a bank card, or PaySuper Checkout may suspect a fraud attempt. If so, the payment status will be cancelled and a PaySuper Checkout notification event will contain an explanatory description.
But some reasons for the failed payments are unclear and uninformative.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>